{"data":[{"question":"It was ________ nice piece of furniture.","a":"such ","b":"so","c":"such a ","d":"so much","answer":"3","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You mustn't drive ________ fast on these roads!","a":"so a ","b":"such","c":"such ","d":"so","answer":"4","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"It was ________ good news.","a":"such ","b":"such a","c":"so ","d":"so much","answer":"1","explain":"- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"There were ________ people.","a":"such ","b":"so","c":"so much ","d":"so many","answer":"4","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)\n- People is countable noun-> use \"many\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She speaks ________ quietly that you can't understand her.","a":"such ","b":"such a","c":"so ","d":"so much","answer":"3","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"We had _______ time that we didn't know what to do.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"such a ","d":"so much","answer":"4","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun + that + result\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"It was ________ loud music that it gave me a headache.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"so much ","d":"such a","answer":"2","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun + that + result\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"It's not safe to live in ________ old house.","a":"such an ","b":"so","c":"such a ","d":"such","answer":"1","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun + that + result\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"It was _______ boring film that we walked out.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"such a ","d":"so much","answer":"3","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun + that + result\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Your brother? He's ________ stupid boy.","a":"such ","b":"so","c":"so much ","d":"such a","answer":"4","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}